<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on Haoming Jiang</title>
    <link>https://hmjianggatech.github.io/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on Haoming Jiang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 18:53:26 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hmjianggatech.github.io/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>My tool for Viewing arXiv Papers</title>
      <link>https://hmjianggatech.github.io/news/arxivviewer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 18:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hmjianggatech.github.io/news/arxivviewer/</guid>
      <description>Recently, the hundreds of daily updates from arXiv make me feel overwhelmed. To help me better digest new machine learning papers, I developed an arXiv paper reading web app: https://arxiv.gtflashlab.com/ .
It gives me an Outlook-like user experience. It allows me to view the latest papers in an efficient, manageable, personalized way. It also provides some basic functions, that help me to manage these papers:
 Reading status: it tells me whether I have viewed the paper or not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Adversarial Training Paper has been Accepted by AISTATS 2021</title>
      <link>https://hmjianggatech.github.io/news/aistats2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2021 22:49:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hmjianggatech.github.io/news/aistats2021/</guid>
      <description>Our Adversarial Training Paper has been Accepted by AISTATS 2021. We propose a learning-to-learn method to improve adversarial training on a variety of tasks.
Reference   Learning to Defense by Learning to Attack 2021 Zhehui Chen*, Haoming Jiang*, Yuyang Shi, Bo Dai, and Tuo Zhao (* Equal Contribution) [arXiv]  The 24th International Conference on Artificial Intelligence and Statistics (AISTATS), 2021   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our BERT Calibration Paper has been Accepted by EMNLP 2020</title>
      <link>https://hmjianggatech.github.io/news/emnlp2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 22:49:01 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hmjianggatech.github.io/news/emnlp2020/</guid>
      <description>We propose to improve BERT model calibration via on-manifold smoothing and off-manifold smoothing.
Reference   Calibrated Fine-Tuning for Pre-trained Language Models via Manifold Smoothing 2020 Lingkai Kong, Haoming Jiang, Yuchen Zhuang, Jie Lyu, Tuo Zhao and Chao Zhang [arXiv]  Conference on Empirical Methods in Natural Language Processing (EMNLP), 2020   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Papers are Accepted by ICML 2020</title>
      <link>https://hmjianggatech.github.io/news/icml2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 22:49:01 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hmjianggatech.github.io/news/icml2020/</guid>
      <description> Two papers are accepted by ICML 2020!
 One is about transformer-based point process model.
The other one is about using smooth policy to improve reinforcement learning in continuous environment.
Reference    Deep Reinforcement Learning with Smooth Policy 2020 Qianli Shen, Yan Li, Haoming Jiang, Zhaoran Wang, Tuo Zhao [arXiv]  International Conference on Machine Learning (ICML), 2020    Transformer Hawkes Process 2020 Simiao Zuo, Haoming Jiang, Zichong Li, Tuo Zhao, Hongyuan Zha [arXiv]  International Conference on Machine Learning (ICML), 2020   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BOND is Accepted by KDD 2020</title>
      <link>https://hmjianggatech.github.io/news/bond/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 22:54:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hmjianggatech.github.io/news/bond/</guid>
      <description>Our recent work on distantly supervised NER is accepted by KDD2020. We are closing the GAP between full supervision and no supervision! See our code here: https://github.com/cliang1453/BOND
 The reuslts (F1 score) are summerized as follows:
   Method CoNLL03 Tweet OntoNote5.0 Webpage Wikigold     Full Supervision 91.21 52.19 86.20 72.39 86.43   Previous SOTA 76.00 26.10 67.69 51.39 47.54   BOND 81.48 48.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Papers are Accepted by ACL 2020</title>
      <link>https://hmjianggatech.github.io/news/acl2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hmjianggatech.github.io/news/acl2020/</guid>
      <description> Two papers are accepted by ACL 2020!
 One is about multidomain NMT using word level mixing model.
The other one is SMART model, leaderboad wining model on GLUE.
Reference    SMART: Robust and Efficient Fine-Tuning for Pre-trained Natural Language Models through Principled Regularized Optimization 2020 Haoming Jiang, Pengcheng He, Weizhu Chen, Xiaodong Liu, Jianfeng Gao and Tuo Zhao [arXiv] [Code]  Annual Conference of the Association for Computational Linguistics (ACL), 2020    Multi-Domain Neural Machine Translation with Word-Level Adaptive Layer-wise Domain Mixing 2020 Haoming Jiang, Chen Liang, Chong Wang and Tuo Zhao [arXiv]  Annual Conference of the Association for Computational Linguistics (ACL), 2020   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State-of-the-art Results on GLUE Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://hmjianggatech.github.io/news/smart/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hmjianggatech.github.io/news/smart/</guid>
      <description>Our recent collabrative work with Microsoft Dynamics 365 AI and Microsoft Research AI (paper, code) achieves state-of-the-art results in 5 of 9 GLUE benchmark tasks and an overall GLUE task performance 89.9, which outperforms all existing models.
 The reuslts are summerized as follows:
   Method CoLA SST MRPC STS-B QQP MNLI-m/mm QNLI RTE WNLI AX Score #params     Previous SOTA 70.8 97.1 91.9/89.2 92.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>